Johnny!
ジョニー！
O-O-Ouch...
だ、大丈夫、滝沢くん？！
Are you okay, Takizawa-kun?
咲？
Saki?
咲！ 大杉どうなった？！ ああっ
Saki, what happened to Oosugi?!
He's okay.
大杉くんは大丈夫
っていうか、そもそもあそこで起きてたこととは
関係なかったらしいの
Actually, it looks like he wasn't involved with what happened there.
Looks like I lost consciousness.
俺、気絶したみたいだけど
Was there anyone else in the hotel when you got there?
咲、ホテルに来たとき他に誰かいなかった？
Nope.
ううん
A dying scream makes no sound
We live a dying dream...
Callin' out to all that I've ever known
If you know what I mean...
Here am I, lost and found...
Episode 8
Searching for the journey
we previously missed out on
It's all that I've ever known...
Callin' out to all
Eden of the East
It's all that I've ever known
Anyway, it's ridiculous of you to think that I met the "Johnny Hunter."
Sorry.
http://animetranscripts.wikispaces.com
Calling him up in-and-out of nowhere
I tried to talk with God to no avail
Catch the wheel that breaks a butterfly
Cry the rain that fills the ocean wide
すいません
そもそも
俺がジョニー狩りに遭うと思うこと自体、どうかしてるよ
でもSOSが書き込まれたのが
例のサイトだったものですから
But the S.O.S. message was written on that board you frequent.
I said if you won't save me
Idiot!
バカ！ 俺があのサイト利用してるってことは秘密だって！
Please don't waste my time
I told you to keep it a secret that I visit that site.
恋愛相談なら
いつでも乗ってあげたのに
Feel free to ask me for advice about relationships.
やめてよ、そういうの
Stop talking about that.
とはいえ、春日の誤解も
あながち間違いだと責められないぞ
Even so, you can't really blame Kasuga for jumping to conclusions and making such a careless mistake.
連絡も取れず、そのカバンの画像を見せられれば
He couldn't contact you,
and anyone who saw the picture of that bag
誰だって書き込みの主が
お前だと思うだろ
would have thought that you were the poster of that thread, right?
Well, I did lose the bag, but even so, normally you'd think of other reasons why you couldn't contact me, right?
確かにこれは俺がなくしたカバンだけど。
にしても
もっと他の事情で連絡が取れないとか
想像するでしょう普通！
現に俺は、内定者研修と称した
飲み会に借り出されていたわけだし
Actually, I was just dragged to a drinking session that was disguised as a "training" session.
They confiscated your cellphone, right?
携帯を取り上げられていたわけね。分かるわ
I know what you went through.
でも、よかったです
先輩のジョニーがちょん切られなくて
But Oosugi, it's great that your Johnny didn't get cut off!
Shut up!
言うな！
となると、カバンは春日と別れた後何者かに拾われ
Basically, someone picked up your bag after Kasuga parted ways with you,
それを拾った男がジョニー狩りに遭遇
and he met the "Johnny Hunter" after that.
ホテルインソムニアに監禁され
SOSの書き込みをしていた…ということか
He was imprisoned in Hotel Insomnia and posted S.O.S. messages on that message board.
So that's what happened?
After that, Takkun barged into the hotel.
その後、たっくんがホテルに突入
However, the "Johnny Hunter" was already gone,
でも、そこにはジョニー狩りの姿はなく
誰かが監禁されていた跡だけが残されていた
and the only thing left were traces indicating that someone was imprisoned there.
World View News
Explosion at Hotel Insomnia
At around 1:10 on the night of the night of 2/17, in To...
...ppongi Hotel Insomnia
...window glass of an occupied room
...ddenly shattered.
Traces of confinement in the room
The "Johnny Hunter" rumored in the area?
With the window glass blown into small fragments, it can
be thought that a sudden shock occurred at the location
which struck the glass.  The windows at the hotel, which
was the scene of the incident, are on the 11th floor
members' rooms and are 3.4 meter high walls which form
the main characteristic of the rooms.  No injuries were
reported due to the falling broken glass, but at a different
time of day it would have been far more severe.
According to the Meteorological Agency, the wind on the day of the incident was light.  Thus, it seems
that some type of explosion occurred at the site but no conclusive evidence was found in the hotel room.
When hotel staff arrived, they found no sign of the woman who was checked into the room.
Only signs that someone had been held captive in the room were found.
Investigation under way into connections with live report posted on a certain site
Due to an indication that this event was connected with the serial killer popularly known in the area
as the "Johnny Hunter", the police are investigating a certain site on which a live report was posted.
Mind if I ask something?
一つ聞いてもいいかな？
その滝沢って奴とは
今後どうするわけ？
What is that Takizawa character planning to do from now on?
俺はこれから会社に顔を出さなきゃならないんだ
I've got to head to the office now.
その後で、咲ちゃんを迎えにいく
I'll meet Saki-chan after that.
で、お前らがその滝沢って男と組むことになるなら
So, if you guys want to cooperate with that Takizawa character,
I won't ever come here again as a member.
残念だけど
このメンバーが一堂に会することは
二度とないだろうね
Why?
なんでよ
俺にだって…プライドぐらいあるから
I still have my pride at the very least.
大杉さん！
Oosugi-san!
So, what should we do?
で、どうするの？
悪い子ではないと思うけど…
I don't think that he's a bad person.
確かに、悪人ではなさそうだが
It's true that he's no scoundrel,
but it's a mystery how he discovered the hotel so quickly and got out of there without being seen.
突然ホテルを突き止めたり
事件後だれにも見咎められずにホテルを出られた謎とか
色々と妙なことがあるのは事実だ
It's true that a lot of weird things have happened.
How about we ask him directly about everything, including what just happened?
その辺りも含めて
なんなら本人に直接聞いてみるのもいいんじゃないか？
これから来るらしいし
Looks like he's coming here soon.
咲からメールあったの？ いつ？
Saki texted you?
When?
大杉が来るちょっと前。もう着くかも
A while before Oosugi arrived.
He might already be here.
大杉…帰しちゃってよかったのかしらね…
I wonder if it's okay to let Oosugi leave now.
咲ちゃん…
Saki... chan...
Was I the only one who didn't know about this?
俺だけが知らなかったのか
Just who are you?!
誰なんだ、お前は
What's he doing?
何あれ…
Oh dear.
ヤダ～
Favorites List
Today's Fortune
Shop
Screen Memo List
Pay Services
Go to URL...
Clear Browser History
Previous Screen
Select
Login
Searching
There are no records of him in Eden?
エデンに登録はないか
Taking picture
Comment Text
Who is he?!
Currently Viewing
Selecao Activity History
Destroy evidence and prevent police
interference at Hotel Insomnia
Balance:
警察を止めてくれたってこと？
She prevented the police from entering?
俺だけが他の奴のこと分かってないのか
I'm the only one who doesn't know what the others are doing?
Looks like it's useless unless I look at the old histories.
やっぱ古い履歴読まないとダメかなぁ
大杉の件は、理解してもらえたのかな？
So, do you understand what happened to Oosugi?
あ、ああ
Y-Yeah.
ならよかった
Great then.
We have some questions for you now.
で、こちらからも
いくつか聞きたいことがあるんだが
登記の件なら、代表は俺でいいよ
It's okay for me to be the representative if you're talking about the registration.
いや…それもあるが
Well, that too, but...
I'll take responsibility for all the difficult stuff.
あとあと面倒なことが起こっても
責任はこっちでかぶるからさ
ああ、でも、権利とか配当とかの受け取りは
However, let's split stuff like rights and shares equally.
均等でいいからね
You're pretty generous.
ずいぶん気前がいいのね
Really?
そう？
However, I've got something to ask you guys in return.
じゃあさ、その代わりと言っちゃなんなんだけど
Is there anyone who can repair this cellphone?
この携帯、修理できる奴いないかな？
It's out of power.
電源が入らなくってさぁ
充電用の穴すら付いていないな
It doesn't even have a place to plug in a charger.
この中に
記憶をなくす前のメールか何かが入ってんのか？
Are there messages and so forth in here from before you lost your memories?
ううん。まあ
Yeah, maybe.
あの、その携帯って二個あったの？
Um, do you have two of those cellphones?
ああ、シネコンで見つけた
I found it in the cinema.
ただ、俺もよく分かんないんだ中身は
But I'm not really sure what's in it.
You've lost your memories after all.
自分の記憶もないんだもんね
Micchon, what's the verdict?
みっちょん、どう？ 直せない？
Fixable?
Phones are different from computers.
携帯はパソコンと違うから
ダメか
It's hopeless?
あ、そうだ
Oh yeah.
板津くんなら何とかなるんじゃない？
Itazu-kun might be able to do something with it, right?
Pants?
パンツかぁ。確かにあいつならできるかもな
True, he might be able to do something.
Who is this "Pants" guy?
なに、その「パンツ」って？
Well, he's someone who gave us a lot of advice when we set up the site for Eden.
いや、エデンのサイトを作るとき
色々とアドバイスをもらった男でね
「京都に神童あり」と謳われた
凄腕ではあるんだが…
He's called The Prodigy from Kyoto and is pretty skilled, but...
が？
But...?
Rumor has it that he's locked himself in a four-and-a-half-mat room located by the River Kamo,
この二年、鴨川沿いの四畳半に引きこもったまま
and hasn't even bothered to come to University.
大学にも行っていない、という噂だ
俺、ちょっとそいつに会ってくるよ
I'll go and meet him.
行くのはいいが
It's fine to look for him, but he probably doesn't want to meet anyone.
たぶん奴は誰とも会わんぞ
なんでよ？ そんなはずはないでしょう
There's no way can that be true.
Hey, are you going to look for him without asking for his address?
おい、住所も聞かずに行く気か？
Would you tell me?
教えてくれんの？
なら、みっちょんを連れてけよ
Bring Micchon along with you then.
She'll at least raise the chances of opening the door that won't open.
開かずの扉が開く可能性が
少しは高まる
Huh?! No way!
ええ！ やだよ～！ あたし、パンツ嫌いだもん！
I hate Pants!
まぁ、そう言うな
Don't say that.
プログラマー同士、あいつとまともに話せるのは
この中でお前しかおらん
Both of you are programmers, so you're the one who's most likely to be able to communicate with him.
ついでに、例の「世間コンピューター」が
完成したのかどうかも聞いてきてくれ
Also, ask him whether the
World Computer is complete yet.
俺からも連絡しとくから
I was going to call him about it.
あたしも一緒に行くよ
I'll go along as well.
前に行ったところと変わってないんでしょ？
板津くんの住処
Itazu-kun is still staying where we visited him last, right?
Will everything be okay?
大丈夫かしら
まあ、スパイとしては頼りないがな…
Well, we can't really depend on them being spies.
スパイって？
Spies?
Sis, even you're curious, right?
おネエだって気にはなるだろ？
滝沢の過去
Takizawa's past, the messages from before he lost his memories...
記憶をなくす前のメール
残ってたら見たいって思わないか？
You'll want to look at them if they're still there, right?
なるほど。だったら僕が
I see.
I'll go then.
Pants won't do a darn thing for you.
お前じゃパンツが動かないんだよ
あれで板津豊って男は
けっこう女の子に弱いからね
The man known as Itazu Yutaka actually has a weakness for women.
男子というものは
みんなそういうものではないんですか？
Isn't that true for all men?
Ouch.
痛っ！
後で板津とみっちょんには
その旨メールで伝達しておく
I'll text Itazu and Micchon later about my intentions.
その間に俺たちは
滝沢の持ってきた書類をもう一度確認しておこう
In the meantime, we'll go over the documents that Takizawa brought over and ensure that they're legit.
奴が詐欺師なら
どこかにほころびが出てくるはずだ
He's bound to screw up somewhere if he's a swindler.
Comment Text
Who is he?!
Currently Viewing
反応なしか…
No response... huh?
Name: Murata Kazuo
Affiliation: Aiji Univ.
Education Dept.  Graduate
DOB: July 10th 1983
Sex: Male
Blood Type: B
Residence: Kanazawa-ken Yokohama-shi Minami
Interests: Film Direction, Sports
Name: Muto Ayumu
Affiliation: Aiji Univ. Economics Dept. Graduate
DOB: October 9th 1985
Sex: Female
Blood Type: A
Residence: Saitama-ken Saitama-shi
Interests: Watching Sports
今さらながら、エデンのシステムには感心する
Even now, I'm still impressed by Eden's system.
Name: Yoshie Shin'ya
Aff: Aiji Univ. Soph. Lit Dept.
DOB: April 13th 1991
Sex: Male
Blood: AB
Res: Tokyo-to Kunitachi-shi Higashi
Int: Sports
Name: Sato Yuika
Aff: Aiji Univ. Soph. Lit Dept.
Sex: Female
Blood: O
Res: Tokyo-to Ota-ku Sakae-cho
Int: Reading
It's able to accurately identify any student from the university.
うちの学生なら
確実に識別するもんな
平澤、お前はすごいよ
Hirasawa, you're amazing.
Currently Viewing
Hasegawa Kazuya, ain't it?
長谷川和也…？
Hasegawa Kazuya?
Hasegawa Kazuya, ain't it?
Hosozawa Naoki
Nah, isn't this guy Kise Koji?
Shibuya Makoto, no doubt about it
I think he's Shibuya too
Currently Viewing
I think he's Okada Shintaro
No, he's gotta be Takizawa Akira!
What's... going on?
なんなんだ…これは…
Hey, what kind of person is Pants?
ねえ、パンツってどんな奴なの？
一言で言えば
自分が世界で一番頭いいと思ってるような奴
Put simply, he's someone who thinks he's the smartest in the world.
Then how is he related to Hirasawa?
んじゃあ、平澤とはどういう仲なの？
一年の時
同じ教授のセミナーで知り合ったのがキッカケみたい
It seems they went to the same seminar when they were in their first year, and met each other by chance there.
会えば怒鳴り合ってるから仲悪そうなんだけど
They yell at each other when they meet, so it looks like they're on bad terms, but they actually get along well.
結構仲いいの
I see.
なるほど
んじゃあ、なんで大学行かなくなっちゃったわけ？
Then why did he stop coming to university?
それがよく分からないんだけど
I'm not really sure about that, but two years ago,
二年前突然
he suddenly called and said: "My only pair of trousers got blown away by the wind, so I will never step out again."
「一張羅のズボンを風に飛ばされたから
もう外には二度と出ない」って連絡が来て
He shut himself in his room after that.
それっきり引きこもっちゃったんだって
Trousers?
ズボン？ 分からんなあ
Makes no sense.
Don't treat what those weirdos say as real.
奇人の言うことは真に受けない方がいいって
「世間の動きをすべて予測してみせる」
It's all because he went around, boasting that "I shall predict all the trends of the world."
なんて豪語していたから、案外それに成功して
世の中に飽きちゃったんだよ、たぶん
He unexpectedly succeeded in doing that and thus lost interest in the world, I guess.
それが世間コンピューター？
Are you talking about the World Computer?
そう
Yup. I'm going to take a short nap.
あたしちょっと寝るね
How's the contract from the real estate agent?
で、そっちの不動産の契約書は？
特に問題なし
I don't see anything out of order.
役所に確認入れたけど
I checked against the municipal one as well, and I didn't discover anything suspicious about Takkun.
たっくんに怪しいところは見当たらないわ
そうか
I see.
All that's left is an official name for the company and to register a seal?
あと必要なのは
正式な社名と印鑑登録くらい？
That's right.
そうね
What should we call the company?
会社名って何てしたらいいのかな？
ただ、あの場所は
いまの俺たちには大きすぎる気がする
But I feel like the place is too big for us now.
We don't need such a huge space since all we need is a minimal amount of space to maintain the system.
必要なのは、システムを保持できる
最低限のスペースであって
巨大な物理空間ではないからな
But we might have some wonderful use for that place.
でも、何か素敵な活用法があるかもよ
ゾンビ映画においては
ショッピングモールは退廃する文明の象徴であり
In zombie flicks, shopping malls represent the final paradise for a small amount of people
who have shut themselves away from a post-apocalyptic civilization.
少数派が引きこもる最後の楽園ですから
我々にとってあそこは
まぎれもない「エデン」なのかもしれませんよ
Thus, that place might essentially become our "Eden."
I see.
なるほど
What would you say if we NEETs are the zombies that are multiplying endlessly?
だが、実は我々ニートこそが
増殖を続けるゾンビだとしたらどうする？
あそこに逃げ込みたいのは
本当は俺たちじゃない誰かかもしれないぞ
Perhaps the one who wants to escape there is someone other than us.
Just what is going on?
どういうことなんだ
あいつ、偽名を使い分けてるってこと？
He's using various aliases?
Currently Viewing
I think he's Okada Shintaro
No, he's gotta be Takizawa Akira!
Hasegawa Kazuya, ain't it?
Okada is a murderer
I think he's Shibuya too
Hosozawa Naoki
Nah, isn't this guy Kise Koji?
Criminal!  Reveal where he lives!
Kise Koji was spotted stealing at explosion sites
Hasegawa...?
Takizawa Akira!  We're gonna kill you!
Shibuya Makoto, no doubt about it
Shibuya Makoto tricked me!
Takizawa Akira!
Kise Kozi
I'll use this opportunity to catch you red-handed.
今のうちに尻尾をつかんでやる！
It's over there.
あそこだよ。二階の角部屋がパンツの住処
Pants lives in the corner on the second floor.
かっこいいじゃん
Looks pretty cool.
Coming in!
お邪魔しま～す！
What should we do?
どうする？
平澤くんから何か指示が来てるんでしょ？
Hirasawa-kun sent you some instructions, right?
He said: "Check Takizawa Akira's old messages in order to find his secrets."
「滝沢朗の秘密を知るためにも
過去のメールを確認せよ」
だってさ
Not just his messages, we have to investigate that cellphone too.
メールだけじゃない
あの携帯が何なのか調べなきゃ
こんちは。パンツくんいますか？
Hello.
Pants-kun, are you around?
Itazu Yutaka
なるほど、「板」に「津」でパンツか…
I see.
He's named Itazu, so that's why you call him Pants...?
Note: Ita can be pronounced "pan"
パンツ豊！ いい名前だ！
Pants Yutaka, that's a nice name!
そんなこと言ったらダメだよ！
もっと持ち上げなきゃ
You can't say that out loud.
You need to flatter him.
Then Mittan, you call him.
じゃあ、みったんが呼び掛けてよ
It's god damn noisy.
やかましいのう
他人の部屋の前でゴチャゴチャと
Who the heck is yakking away in front of someone's home?
Oh? Micchon, you're here?
なんなあ。みっちょん着いたんか
Oh, you're Pants-kun?
君がパンツくん？
I've no interest in you!
お前には興味ない
The lady from the bakery is here too?
パン屋のお姉ちゃんもおるんか？
Yeah. It's been a while. How have you been?
ええ。久しぶりだけど、元気？
I'm sorry, but could you get me the weekly pictorial and literary magazines at the convenience store?
悪いんじゃが、コンビニ行って
写真週刊誌と文芸誌買うてきてや
Eh? Can't you buy them online?
ネットで買いなよ
True, but I'm busy.
そがな余裕はないんじゃ
消えたニートの行方から
迂闊な月曜日の真相
Things like the whereabouts of missing NEETs, the truth behind Careless Monday,
the testimony given by a sex offender who survived having his dick cut off,
果てはチンコ切られて生還した性犯罪者の証言まで
and the Prime Minister saying "mercy" are keeping me very busy.
首相のギャフン発言からこっち
えらい急展開じゃ
通販届くのを待っとれんわ
I can't wait for them to arrive by mail.
お前は携帯置いて帰れ
As for you, leave your cellphone here and leave.
I'll salvage whatever I can when I'm free.
暇んときサルベージしたるけえ
東京で気長に待っちょれ！
Wait patiently in Tokyo.
What are you up to?
何だよ…
まあまあ、買ってきてあげてよ
Oh well.
Just get him those magazines.
行こう、みっちょん
Let's go, Micchon.
そがなんしても、お前とは会わんどぉ！
I won't meet you even if you do that.
Hey, Itazu.
なあ、板津
お前、セレソン関係の事件に興味あるの？
Are you interested in things to do with Selecao?
Don't get interested in my noble research!
わしのこの高尚な調べ事に興味持つなや！
You'll corrupt the data!
データが腐るけ！
だいたいのう、ビンテージジーンズはいとるような奴に
首突っ込んでほしゅうないわ！
Moreover, I don't want people who wear vintage jeans to poke their nose in my affairs!
しかも、セレソンじゃあ？
Also, did you say Selecao?
それじゃあ言うて
野党のボンクラ議員の発言から最近覚えた口じゃろうが！
Isn't that a catchphrase you learned about recently because of that dumbass opposition Diet member?
Well, maybe.
まあね
でもさあ
But...
俺がセレソンなんだって言ったら
お前どうする？
what would you do if I said that I'm a Selecao?
雑誌買ってったら部屋に入れてくれるかな？
Will he let us into his room now that we've bought him the magazines?
Let's give up since I don't want to enter it.
入りたくないからいいよ…
But we're in trouble if he doesn't fix that phone...
でも、携帯直してもらわないと困るし
そうだ！ 板津くんにジャージ買ってってあげようか！
I know, what about buying a jersey for Itazu-kun?
外出できるように
He'll be able to come out then.
それ、すっごい嫌味だと思うけど？
Doing that will probably make him feel very uncomfortable.
Huh? Why?
なんで？
It's not as if he really shut himself in his room because he lost his trousers... I think.
だって、本当にズボンがなくなったから
引きこもっているわけじゃないでしょう
たぶん
そっか
I see.
確かにのう
It's true...
He's saying "Say mercy."
「ギャフン言え」言うとる
だろ？
See?
When did you notice that?
お前、どうやって気づいたんなら？
俺がやったからさ
I was the one that made him do it.
Be it the incident about the twenty thousand missing NEETs which people confused with the Johnny Hunter,
他にも
二万人のニート失踪と混同して語られてる
ジョニー狩りのことや
昨日六本木で起きた
いくつかの事故とセレソンとの関係性についても
and yesterday's incident at Roppongi,
or even how they are all tied to the Selecao,
I can probably tell you quite a lot about them.
結構詳しく話せると思うよ
ジョニー狩りとニート失踪を混同して語るんは
ネット上じゃむしろデフォルト
Thinking that the Johnny Hunter and NEET incidents were the same was a common theory on the Internet.
お前、何者なら？
Who are you?
だから、セレソンなんだって
I've already told you that I'm a Selecao.
開けてくれよ、板津
Open up, Itazu.
You should believe me after you analyze this phone.
この携帯を解析してみたら
俺の言ってることの意味が分かるはずだからさ
What's with that phone?
その携帯、何なんや？
12人のセレソンが一個ずつ持ってる
魔法の携帯ってとこかな
Each of the twelve Selecao has one.
You can call it a magical phone.
Weren't there only eleven Selecao?
セレソンは11人じゃないんか？
何なんだ、ここは？
What happened here?
Comment Text
Who is he?!
Currently Viewing
I think he's Okada Shintaro
No, he's gotta be Takizawa Akira!
Hasegawa Kazuya, ain't it?
Takizawa Akira!
Okada is a murderer
I think he's Shibuya too
Hosozawa Naoki
Kise Kozi
Nah, isn't this guy Kise Koji?
Criminal!  Reveal where he lives!
Kise Koji was spotted stealing at explosion sites
Hagesawa...?
I'll kill you, Takizawa Akira!
Shibuya Makoto, no doubt about it
Shibuya Makoto tricked me!
I agree, Shibuya is a criminal
I called him HOSOZAWA
Hey, isn't Kise Kozi also Hosozawa?
Hosozawa, Hasegawa, Kise, Shibuya, Okada.
細澤、長谷川、黄瀬、渋谷、岡田…
I know, he's Shibuya Makoto!
Post reported due to Hagesawa
I remember him well, it's Okada Shintaro!
The names are different but they all refer to Takizawa.
名前は違うけど
全部滝沢と同じ人物だ…
咲ちゃん、そいつは絶対危ないよ！
Saki-chan, he's definitely dangerous!
Received
Sent
Kasuga Haruo
Sissy
Hirasawa Kazuomi
Miyano Koji
Mr. Ono
はい、平澤です
Hello, this is Hirasawa.
Hirasawa, is Saki-chan with you now?
平澤？ いま咲ちゃんそこにいるか？
Nope, she went to Kyoto to take care of something.
いや、ちょっと訳あって京都に行ってる
Kyoto?! Why?
京都？ なんで？
例の滝沢の件でさ
It's about Takizawa.
パンツのところに行ってもらったんだ
She went to Pants' place.
滝沢と一緒なのか？
Takizawa is with her?
ああ
Yeah.
Idiot!
バカ！ なんてことしたんだ！
Why did you do that?!
みっちょんも一緒だし
別に問題ないだろう
Micchon is with them too, so there shouldn't be a problem, right?
そういうことじゃない！
今すぐ豊洲のシネコンに来てみろ！
That's not what I'm talking about!
Come to the cinema at Toyosu immediately!
それに、俺がエデンのサイトにアップした
滝沢朗の書き込み、見てみろよ！
Also, look at the entry about Takizawa that I posted up on Eden!
He's a criminal!
あいつは犯罪者なんだよ！
He might even be connected to some shocking incidents!
それも、もしかしたら
とんでもない事件に関わってるかもしれないんだ！
Look over there.
あれ
この二年、ズボンの喪失を理由に隠遁生活続けてきた
For the past two years, I continued to live in seclusion using the excuse that I lost my pants.
Even so, I wish to return to bathe under the sun;
ほいじゃが、同胞言うて同情する
it might be because they are the same as me or because I sympathize with them,
全国二万のニート失踪を機に
that I want to use the opportunity from the disappearance of the twenty thousand NEETs
その謎をこの四畳半から解き明かし
to unravel the truth behind that incident in this four-and-a-half-mat room.
今一度お天道様の元に戻ろういうてもんどり打ってきたこのワシを
You better not be lying to me.
よもや騙そういうんじゃなかろうのう
Sure.
夜は封印
戸惑い混じれば終わる
迷い出すぐらいならいっそ
わ     け
理由も捨てよう
また夢に溺れる
不確かに続いてく未来
まだ君を許せる
意味を知れる
耳を澄ますための夜
その理由を真似て変われる
君の呼吸を知るために
未来の根を切っても構わない